Wait.
ちょっと待って。
&gt;&gt; What's wrong?
&gt;&gt; どうしたの？
&gt;&gt; When did this turn into a cooking show all of a sudden?
&gt;&gt; いつからクッキングショーになったの？
&gt;&gt; Since we had to talk about methods?
&gt;&gt; それはメソッドを学ぶためよ。
&gt;&gt; Care to explain, Rachael Ray?
&gt;&gt; レイチェル・レイさん、説明してもらえるかな？
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] Well, have you ever baked a cake before?
&gt;&gt; ケーキをつくったことはある？
&gt;&gt; I have eaten a cake before.
&gt;&gt; 食べたことはあるよ。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; じゃあ
Well, then you're fully qualified for this.
これはあなたにぴったりだと思うわ
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; そうなんだ。
&gt;&gt; All you have to do to bake a cake is to put in flour, sugar.
&gt;&gt; ケーキは小麦粉と砂糖を入れれば作れるのよ。
&gt;&gt; The ingredients.
&gt;&gt; 材料だね。
Okay.
分かった。 &gt;&gt;そう材料。
Yeah.
その通り。
And then you follow the instructions of the recipe.
そしてレシピにしたがうだけよ。
&gt;&gt; Okay. &gt;&gt; And then out comes a cake.
&gt;&gt; わかった。&gt;&gt;それでケーキができるんだね。
&gt;&gt; Like this?
&gt;&gt; こんな感じ？
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; そう。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Well
&gt;&gt; わかった。
connect the analogy to the methods one more time.
これとメソッドとどんな関係があの？
&gt;&gt; Okay. Sure so for
&gt;&gt; それは、
a method you can put in inputs.
メソッドにはインプットがあるわ。
&gt;&gt; Like we did the quantity for the display method?
&gt;&gt; displayメソッドのquantity見たいにかい？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, and then you execute the instructions of the method.
&gt;&gt; そう、そしてメソッドに従って実行するの。
&gt;&gt; Okay, almost like the recipe for making a cake?
&gt;&gt; 分かった、ケーキのレシピに従うようにだね？
&gt;&gt; Mm-hm.
&gt;&gt; その通り。
Then you can have the output value returned.
そしてアウトプットを受け取ることができるの。
&gt;&gt; Outputs, they are delicious.
&gt;&gt; アウトプットっておいしいんだね。
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Let's look up more information
&gt;&gt; メソッドのインプットパラメータについて
about input parameters for methods.
もっと学んでみましょう
I'm going to do a Google search for Jjava method parameter.
JavaメソッドのパラメータをGoogleで検索してみます。
The first link looks good so I'm going to click on it.
最初のリンクがよさそうですね。
Now this article talks about passing information to a method.
メソッドに情報を渡すことについて書いてあります。
Here's a code snippet that computes the monthly payments for a home loan.
これは住宅ローンの月額を計算するコードです。
It has four input parameters, loan amount, interest rate, future value
４つのインプットがあり、ローンの額、利子、将来額、
of the loan, as well as the number periods of the length of the loan.
そしてローンの期間です。
And then inside this method we see that we can use these input parameters
メソッドの中では、そのインプットが計算をするために
simply as variables to do our math calculations.
変数として使われています。
When we call the compute payment method,
computePaymentメソッドを呼ぶ時には、
we have to make sure we pass in the inputs in this specific order.
インプットをこの順番に渡すことが肝心です。
So the loan amount has to go first, and then the rate and so on.
ローンの額、利子、というように記入します。
For the quiz in this section,
今回の問題では、
you'll have the chance to review this article in more detail.
これを詳細に読むことになります。
Within the main activity of the desk Java app,
Just JavaアプリのMainActivityの中で、
we're going to be modifying the display quantity method and
displayQuantityメソッドとそのインプットを変更して、
the input parameter to give you some practice.
練習をしてみたいと思います。
Notice that in the decrement method of our app,
アプリのdecrementメソッドでは、
what we call the display quantity method,
displayQuantityメソッドを呼ぶときに、
we're passing the quantity variable over as input to this method.
quantityという変数を渡していることに注目してください。
But the input parameter is called 'number', so
インプットパラメータはnumberとなっています。
whenever we want to refer to this input, we just have to say number.
このインプットを使いたいときには、numberを 使わなければいけません。
Now technically we could have used the global quantity variable within this
ここで、インプットパラメータを使わずに、
method instead of passing it as an input parameter.
quantityというグローバル変数を 使うこともできます。
but for the purposes of teaching you about input parameters,
しかし、インプットパラメータを学ぶために、
let's just leave it like this.
このままにしておきましょう。
I can change this call to the display quantity method so
このdisplayMethodのコールを
it passes input, the number 30.
３０という数字を渡すように変更します。
This is valid because it still matches the input data type.
これはインプットのタイプと合っているので大丈夫です。
So in the decrement method when we call it display quantity,
decrementメソッドでdisplayQuantityメソッドを呼ぶと、
it will jump down here and it will execute these instructions, and
ここにきて、この指令を実行します。
the variable number will have the value of 30.
ここで変数は３０になります。
I'll run it on my device to show you, so now when I run the minus button on my
端末で実行してみます。マイナスボタンを押すと、
app, it will display a quantity of 30 here.
３０という料を表示します。
So let me try that.
やってみましょう。
There. And it actually happened like that.
ちゃんと機能していますね。
I can also create a different variable and pass that as an input to the method.
もう一つ編巣を作って、それを渡すこともできます。
Here I've created a local variable called some quantity, and
ここにローカル変数を作って、
I initialized it to 100.
１００としました。
I passed this variable as input to this method,
この変数をメソッドのインプットとして記入します。
and now the number variable inside here has a value of 100.
これでnumber変数は１００となりました。
Let me run this on the device.
マイナスボタンを押すと、１００となるはずです。
And it does.
ちゃんと機能していますね。
These are just some things you can do to experiment with
メソッドのインプットを渡す練習のために、
passing in different inputs to a method.
このようなことを試してみてもいいでしょう。
As you work with input parameters,
インプットパラメータを扱ううえで、
another term that you might come across is arguments.
耳にするもう一つの単語はargumentです。
When you call a method,
メソッドを呼ぶとき、
the inputs being passed to that method are called the arguments.
そのメソッドに渡されるインプットは、argumentといいます。
Now this is kind of a funny word.
少しおかしな単語なんですが、
Because when you think of arguments, you think of people yelling and
argumentと聞くと、なにか口論している
cursing at each other.
イメージが湧きますよね。
But this is not like that.
でもこれは違います。
Arguments are simply the inputs being passed to a method.
argumentは単純にメソッドに渡されるインプットです。
Input parameters are the actual inputs in your method declaration and
インプットパラメータはメソッドの宣言で使われるもので、
those are the variables that are used within your method.
メソッドの中で使われる変数です。
So that's a slight difference between input parameter and arguments.
なので、インプットパラメータとargumentは少し違います。
In any case, go ahead and read the article and
それでは、メソッドのパラメータについて、この記事と、
the instructor notes about method parameters.
指導書を読んでみてください。
Then go ahead and experiment with the code in your app.
そして自分のアプリで試してみてください。
First try to rename the number input parameter
まずdisplayQuantityメソッドの中で、
within the display quantity method declaration.
numberというインプットパラメータを変えてください。
Just simply give it a different variable name.
違う変数の名前を与えてください。
Then go ahead and fix any errors, and then run the app again.
そしてエラーを解消して、実行してみてください。
For the next test, go ahead and change the data type
次のテキストでは、numberインプットパラメータのタイプを
of the number input parameter from an int to something else like String.
intから、例えばstringなど違ったタイプにしてみてください。
Observe what happens and then go ahead and undo the change.
何が起こるかを見て、元に戻してください。
If you want to experiment with other things, go right ahead.
他にも試したいことがあればぜひやってみてください。
For example, if you have a question,
これをしたらどうなるだろう、と思ったら、
what would happen if I do x, then just go ahead and try it.
それを試してみてください。